In the age of the internet, there’s no such thing as a private debate.
在互联网时代，不存在私下辩论这回事。
But is that bad for science?
但这对科学不利吗？
Some scientists have had concerns.
一些科学家一直心存顾虑。
When debates in any sector move beyond the halls of universities and government agencies, there’s potential for information to be used incorrectly, leading to public confusion; yet, open debate can also promote communication between the scientific community and the public.
任何领域的辩论一旦走出大学和政府机构的殿堂，信息就有可能遭到错误使用，从而造成公众困惑；然而，公开辩论也能促进科学界与公众之间的交流。
Recent open debates on scientific research, health, and policy have aroused greater public attention and encouraged more diverse voices.
最近围绕科学研究、健康和政策展开的公开辩论引起了公众更多的关注，也鼓励了更加多元的声音。
If this trend spurs scientists to agree more quickly about the best solutions to our problems—and at the same time helps the public observe the process of scientific discourse more clearly—then this is good for everyone, including scientists.
如果这一趋势促使科学家更快地就我们所面临问题的最佳解决办法达成一致，同时又帮助公众更清楚地观察科学讨论的过程，那么这对包括科学家在内的所有人都有好处。
A recent debate published in The New York Times discussed the question of how quickly medicine should be developed and produced.
《纽约时报》最近刊登的一场辩论探讨了药物应该以多快的速度研发和生产的问题。
Issues such as the safety of the product and the perception of the public were examined and considered.
诸如产品的安全性、公众的看法等问题得到了审视和考量。
But some experts worried that such public speculation might lead people to believe that disagreement about the details meant a lack of adequate scientific consensus over the safety and efficacy of modern-day medicine.
但一些专家担心，这种公开的推测可能会让人们认为，在细节上存在分歧，就意味着对现代药物的安全性和有效性缺乏足够的科学共识。
The anxiety seems misplaced.
这种担忧似乎是多余的。
Gone are the days of going to a conference and debating scientific issues, and that’s good because those gatherings were not diverse enough and excluded many important voices.
去开会、在会上辩论科学问题的日子已经一去不复返了，这是好事，因为那些聚会不够多元，把许多重要的声音排除在外。
These days, the public can access debates about science regardless of where they take place.
如今，有关科学的辩论无论在哪里进行，公众都能接触到。
For many scientists, public debate is a new frontier and it may feel like a place with few restraints or rules, but rather than avoiding such conversations, let the debates be transparent and vigorous, wherever they are held.
对许多科学家来说，公开辩论是一个新领域，可能让人感觉像是一个几乎没有约束或规则的地方；但与其回避这类对话，不如让这些辩论无论在哪里举行，都透明而热烈。
If the public is to understand that science is an honorably self-correcting process, the idea that science is a fixed set of facts in a textbook needs to be dismissed.
如果要让公众明白科学是一个可敬的自我纠错过程，就需要摒弃这样一种观念：科学是教科书里一套固定不变的事实。
With the validity of science coming under attack, there’s a need for scientific debates to be perceived as open and true to life.
在科学的正确性正遭受攻击之际，有必要让人们把科学辩论看作是公开的、真实的。
Let everyone see the noisy, messy deliberations that advance science and lead to decisions that benefit us all.
让每个人都看到那些喧闹而杂乱的商讨吧，它们推动科学进步，带来对我们所有人都有益的决定。